Guide to the Abu Dhabi Film Festival Collection AD.MC.006
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- 2014 Abu Dhabi Film Festival, 320
  - New Horizons, 3312
    - Whiplash, 2014; 3337 (Disk ADFF 2014-28)
      Director: Damien Chazelle (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Whiplash
  - Short Film Competition, 3305
    - The Baby, 2014; 3306 (Disk ADFF 2014-2)
      Total Running Time 00:15:00
      Director: Ali Asgari (Iran, Italy)
      Original Title: La bambina (Bache)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Baby
    - The Bionic Girl, 2014; 3336 (Disk ADFF 2014-27)
      Director: Stéphanie Cabdevila (France)
      Original Title: La Fille Bionique
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Bionic Girl
    - Dear Hassan, 2014; 3334 (Disk ADFF 2014-25)
      Director: Axel Salvatori-Sinz (France)
      Original Title: Cher Hassan
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Dear Hassan
    - Dinosaurs Don't Live Here Anymore, 2014; 3350 (Disk ADFF 2014-41)
      Director: Miguel Ángel Pérez Blanco (Spain)
      Original Title: Los dinosaurios ya no viven aquí
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Dinosaurs Don't Live Here Anymore
    - Koshk, 2014; 3346 (Disk ADFF 2014-37)
    - The Man with a Dog, 2014; 3333 (Disk ADFF 2014-24)
      Director: Kamal Lazraq (France)
      Original Title: Moul lkelb (L'homme au chien)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Man With A Dog
    - Xenos, 2014; 3351 (Disk ADFF 2014-42)
      Director: Mahdi Fleifel (Denmark, Greece, United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Xenos
  - Showcase, 3317
    - Bears, 2014; 3320 (Disk ADFF 2014-12)
      Director: Alastair Fothergill, Keith Scholey (United Kingdom, USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Bears
    - Energized, 2014; 3339 (Disk ADFF 2014-30)
      Director: Hubert Canaval (Austria)
      German, English, French
      Original Title: Macht energie
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Energized
    - Food Chains, 2014; 3322 (Disk ADFF 2014-14)
      Director: Sanjay Rawal (USA)
      English, Spanish
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Food Chains
    - The Great Invisible, 2014; 3352 (Disk ADFF 2014-43)
      Director: Margaret Brown (USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Great Invisible
    - The Homesman, 2014; 3318 (Disk ADFF 2014-10)
      Total Running Time: 02:02:00
      Director: Tommy Lee Jones (France, USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Homesman
    - Labyrinthus, 2014; 3349 (Disk ADFF 2014-39)
      Director: Douglas Boswell (Belgium, Netherlands)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Labyrinthus
    - My Old Lady, 2014; 3319 (Disk ADFF 2014-11)
      Director: Israel Horovitz (United Kingdom, France, USA)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | My Old Lady
    - Two Days, One Night, 2014; 3330 (Disk ADFF 2014-21)
      Director: Jean-Pierre Dardenne, Luc Dardenne (Belgium, France, Italy)
      French, Arabic
      Original Title: Deux jours, une nuit
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Two Days, One Night
    - Winter Sleep, 2014; 3341 (Disk ADFF 2014-32)
      Total Running Time: 03:16:00
      Director: Nuri Bilge Ceylan (Turkey, France, Germany
      Turkish, English
      Original Title: Kis uykusu
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Winter Sleep
  - Special Programmes, 3307
    - The Color of Pomegranates, 1968; 3326 (Disk ADFF 2014-17)
      Total Running Time: 01:17:00
      Director: Sergei Parajanov (Armenia)
      Armenian
      Original Title: Sayat nova (a.k.a. Nran guyne)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Color Of Pomegranates
    - Day for Night, 1973; 3321 (Disk ADFF 2014-13)
      Director: François Truffaut (France)
      Original Title: La nuit américaine
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Day For Night
    - Delice Paloma, 2007; 3314 (Disk ADFF 2014-7)
      Total Running Time: 02:14:00
      Director: Nadir Moknèche (Algeria, France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Délice Paloma
    - A Fistful of Dollars, 1964; 3327 (Disk ADFF 2014-18)
      Director: Sergio Leone (Italy, Spain, Germany)
      Original Title: Per un pugno di dollari
      Catalog Record: GetIt | A Fistful of Dollars
    - A Hard Day's Night, 1964; 3316 (Disk ADFF 2014-9)
      Director: Richard Lester (United Kingdom)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | A Hard Day's Night
    - Inch'Allah Dimanche, 2001; 3338 (Disk ADFF 2014-29)
      Director: Yamina Benguigui (Algeria, France)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Inch'Allah Dimanche
    - Jules and Jim, 1962; 3329 (Disk ADFF 2014-20)
      Original Title: Jules et Jim
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Jules and Jim
    - The Polish Bride, 1998; 3340 (Disk ADFF 2014-31)
      Director: Karim Traïdia (Algeria, Netherlands)
      Dutch, German, Polish
      Original Title: De poolse bruid
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Polish Bride
    - Salut Cousin!, 1996; 3308 (Disk ADFF 2014-3)
      Director: Merzak Allouache (Algeria, France, Belgium, Luxembourg)
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Salut Cousin!
    - Small Change, 1976; 3331 (Disk ADFF 2014-22)
      Total Running Time: 01:44:00
      Original Title: L' argent de poche
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Small Change
    - Waiting for Happiness, 2002; 3311 (Disk ADFF 2014-5)
      Director: Abderrahmane Sissako (Mauritania, France)
      Hassaniya, Bambara, French
      Original Title: Heremakono
      Catalog Record: GetIt | Waiting For Happiness
    - The Wild Child, 1970; 3332 (Disk ADFF 2014-23)
      Original Title: L' enfant sauvage
      Catalog Record: GetIt | The Wild Child